TYPHOON FAMILY
This way.
-What happened?
-Why did the lights go out?
-Find the switch.
-Just go!
You damn bastards!
-Ms. Cha!
-What's going on?
-Hey.
-Mr. Kang.
-Hurry!
-Run!
Quickly!
-Ms. Cha!
-Run for your life!
Hurry! Hurry up!
What do we do now?
-Quickly!
-Speed it up!
Quickly! Hurry!
Just go. Move!
Help her.
-But they're…
-Darn it.
Hey, wait for me. Oh, shoot.
I brought some red ginseng drinks
for your energy.
-That's lovely.
-Thank you.
Here, here.
Your flying kick was amazing, Mr. Go.
-I sure showed them.
-Here you go, Ms. Cha.
I'll take a pass.
Come on, Seon-taek.
Drink this before you go.
Ms. Cha.
You're overdoing it.
A bookkeeper doesn't make enough
to afford that nameplate.
Why not? It's because I'm fond of him.
Not as a man, of course.
Mr. Kang is here. Come on out, everyone.
Okay.
Ms. Cha, come on.
I'm coming!
CELEBRATING THE NEW OFFICE
CEO KANG JIN-YOUNG
What's up? Did you find something?
PROMISSORY NOTE
What is it?
Tell us what it is.
"Creditor Kang Jin-young."
"Debtor Pyo Bak-ho."
This is it.
It's the promissory note.
Is it the real thing?
Yes, this is the one.
I finally found the promissory note.
Mr. Koo.
Goodness.
Oh, dear.
Gosh, Ms. Cha!
-It's all good now.
-Oh, my goodness.
My gosh.
Mr. Kang…
He had put it in here,
in the nameplate I gave him.
I gave this to him.
This is so good.
Look, Tae-poong.
Your father's name was broken in half.
How can you be eating ramyeon right now?
It's so good, though.
I mean, I am sad.
But this is so good.
Just let him eat. He must be starving
after such a huge incident.
-For you, Ms. Oh.
-Thank you.
Giving you one whole egg means
I'm giving you my all.
You can't give her the whole egg!
We're supposed to share!
There weren't many eggs to begin with.
-You're being temperamental.
-Ms. Cha, join us before it gets soggy.
The noodles are already overcooked.
What about kimchi?
-Come on.
-Kimchi, my foot.
Steal some for us!
Tae-poong…
Thank you.
Anyway.
It was 30% of his shares at stake.
I can see
why he made such a fuss to get this.
This was the all-powerful document.
It was many years ago,
when he operated a regular route
to Yokohama with just one ship
and he got into a huge accident.
Everyone said he would go bankrupt.
And Mr. Kang must've lent him money
back then with shares as collateral.
Then let's use this
to get our business back.
I mean, how long
do we have to stay separated?
We're here together already.
And we get to enjoy
this delicious meal together.
Isn't this great? Isn't it delicious?
Can we call this a proper meal?
-Should we add some rice?
-Add or no?
-Should I get some leftover rice?
-Yes or no?
FINAL EPISODE
WE MET THE BLUEBIRD, AND LIFE GOES ON
Now, these punks are truly frightening.
Look at this.
They've done
this much research and investigation.
How did they…
Wait, this is…
It's my childhood family photo.
-What?
-I can't believe it.
-Oh, my.
You were cute as a child.
BUSINESS LICENSE
FACTORY REGISTRATION CERTIFICATE
Look at this.
What's a PMP?
Wait.
PMP?
-Yes?
-What's wrong?
This is a legendary video player
that even insiders like me
have only heard about through rumors.
It's as small as the palm of your hand,
and you can watch videos on it,
such as dramas and movies.
It'll probably ruin your eyesight.
It looks like a confidential document
from a company abroad.
A PMP with a camera as its feature
will be launched for the first time,
but what's funny is this.
The temperature rises up to 48 degrees
Celsius after 30 minutes of use.
-Did you say 48 degrees?
-Yes.
-Isn't that hot enough to be a handwarmer?
-Right.
How are you supposed to use that?
But they'll be in trouble
if they fail to launch it this time.
Because their stock price doubled
after the launch announcement.
Overheating.
Overheating…
That's quite a lot.
PATENT CERTIFICATE
"Micro cooling fan for cameras."
Small cameras won't function
without cooling devices to cool them down.
What's up?
A cooling fan!
THE PATENT KING OF A SMALL NATION
INVENTS THE COOLING FAN TECHNOLOGY
-Mr. Bae, you brought that, right?
-What?
Yes, right.
You told me to bring it, so I did.
JULY 3RD, 1998
What is he holding?
My father made that.
That's it. That's a cooling fan.
It's like he's shooting a Cantonese movie
with that cooling fan.
That's it. That's what they need.
If not, they can't launch their product.
Are you saying they pushed
a factory into bankruptcy
and auctioned it off just for this patent?
-These punks should be cursed by fate!
-Besides, they're working together.
Look at this.
MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING
Look at what Pyo Merchant Marine has done.
It says their ship.
They bought a ship.
They're a den of evil.
He never answers the damn question.
Well, at least
we found out what they're after.
So why don't we give them what they want
and make a deal to get what we want?
Look.
If they're buying the factory
because they need this,
what if they no longer need this?
Well, that's true.
How can we
make the patent unnecessary for them?
-My gosh!
-Goodness.
-Then it should no longer be patented.
-Yes.
Think about it. If we can use it,
the factory across the street can use it,
and Mark can use it,
it's no longer patented.
Then he won't need to buy the factory.
Release the technology to the public?
You two are such a perfect duo.
You two have such good teamwork,
people might think you two are dating.
How many days until the auction?
-I'm not sure.
-How many days?
Three days.
An auction? Just thinking about it
is making me break out in a sweat.
Well, we either go big or go home.
-No, we have to get it this time.
-Really?
Can we share our offer
and ask them to back down?
-That hurts!
-You might as well sell your place.
-Never stop.
-So we must go!
Ma-jin, forget something?
-Ma-jin loses.
-What now?
-Take the blow!
PYO BAK-HO MERCHANT SHIP BLUEPRINT
CEO PYO HYUN-JUN
Freckles!
I need iced coffee!
PLEASE KEEP THE DOOR CLOSED
I already had your iced coffee ready.
What the heck?
Please excuse me, sir.
All good.
-Where's Freckles?
-It's her day off.
Darn it. Says who?
Jeez. I liked Freckles' recipe,
what was it again?
Three-two-three? That was good.
Did you spit in this?
I'm not that kind of a man.
You're too much.
Get out.
-What do you want? Go.
-I'll go.
Where did she go without telling me?
SEIZED
-Is it two days until the auction?
-Yes.
-It's for a new business, right?
Why do we have to do this?
It's a factory auction,
so we have to do it as a business entity.
Right, Pyo is currently
the CEO of Typhoon Trading.
Let me see that.
Okay, copies of IDs.
-Copies.
-Power of attorney.
Okay. Good.
-That document.
-Yes, right.
-What should we name the business?
-The name?
Well, it's only temporary.
MISEON TRADING
"Miseon Trading."
Anyway, I'm not sure if the owner here
will agree to release the patent.
We'll just have to trust him.
Sir, what do you say?
All right.
You have a point.
It's still a shame, isn't it?
No, that's not how I feel.
It's not a shame.
It's much better and proper
for you to do that with it
than for me to clench onto it.
It just feels futile, that's all.
All of these feel like my own children,
and I had kept the patent with me
in case it could help
my employees in the future.
But it feels like this is what
has been holding me back in the end.
Would I have avoided this if I had let go
of my greed a long time ago?
My father would've said…
that you weren't withering.
This technology
is about to bloom
and bear fruit.
Is that so?
All right.
It's also a parent's job
to let the child go and grow.
But why are you going out of your way
to help another person so much?
I'm grateful for it,
but isn't it hard for you?
Well, I've never thought about it.
You know,
Typhoon Trading needs Dabontech
to be able to sell these.
A factory is needed
for a trading company to exist.
So let's keep doing this together, sir.
You're a great businessman.
NEW PRODUCT ANNOUNCEMENT BOARD
CREATE NEW POST
TITLE: DABONTECH PATENT DISCLOSURE
I SHARE THE "MICRO COOLING FAN
FOR CAMERA" TECHNOLOGY BY DABON HERE.
I can't believe it.
Zero typos?
UPLOADING
Live long and prosper.
What is this?
Wow, this is fricking rad!
It's true.
Who released this?
Sir!
Hey, Mr. Kim.
Don't mention it.
Put it to good use.
What? Other patents?
What kind of crazy talk is this?
Stop talking total nonsense!
I'm hanging up!
DONGJU DAILY
Mr. Jang, you were waiting out here.
Please take care of this.
14 HOURS UNTIL THE AUCTION
TWO HOURS UNTIL THE AUCTION
DONGJU DAILY
INSAN DISTRICT COURT
ONE HOUR UNTIL THE AUCTION
Will you hurry up?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
What the heck is he doing?
Just run him over.
I told you to leave it open.
Didn't you get the message?
I'm sorry!
Stop saying sorry and open the darn thing!
-I'm sorry!
-Stop saying sorry!
-Yes, I'm sorry.
-What's with him?
-Hey, you go and open it.
-Yes, sir.
I found it!
I found it. It's right here. I found it.
I'm sorry.
Has he lost it?
All done.
Hey, just go.
Why, you…
Hey.
The player
has left late.
INSAN DISTRICT COURT
Here you go.
This is what you drink in Korea.
I'm serious.
And take this too.
I'm done with it.
It's our culture.
When we're done with a paper, we switch.
DONGJU DAILY
What do you think?
How interesting.
I knew you could speak Korean.
What the heck is this punk doing?
Damn it.
Why the heck are you here?
Hey.
I'm asking why you're here.
Why else? I'm here to join the auction.
Sorry? Can the penniless
enter auctions these days?
Why are you so full of prejudices?
I won the lottery.
Good luck to us.
What's our limit?
What we can use right away
after the down payment on the ship--
IN SESSION
TODAY'S TRIAL
COURTROOM: 417
CCTV FACTORY AND ALL FACILITIES
DABONTECH
Case number 1998CE9854-985.
Miseon Trading?
Miseon Trading bids 30 million won.
And Pyo Merchant Marine.
10,000 won.
Sold to Miseon Trading.
PATENT ABANDONED! LET'S SAVE US ALL!
DABONTECH RELEASES COOLING FAN PATENT
Isn't this good for you?
You got what you desperately wanted
without paying a penny.
What's available to everyone
can't be called a technology.
Because I am
a trader.
I sell things, not technologies.
A trader?
Feel free to bring your overheated PMP
if you don't think you can sell them.
I'll sell it to the North Pole if I must.
TYPHOON TRADING
THE REAL CEO KANG TAE-POONG
Have you lost your mind?
What, 10,000 won?
How dare you?!
What the heck is he saying?!
Hey, forget that.
Did he just smile?
Did you just smile?
-I've been too nice to that punk.
-Wait, sir!
-Calm down.
-Hey!
SEIZED
The machines, the business, and the people
will all go back to their rightful places!
We'll all go back to our rightful places!
Hooray!
Good job, sir.
Thank you so much.
Good work.
We can keep working here!
What? You're going back?
Hey.
What's with him? Why is Mark leaving?
Is he leaving?
-I'll bring some antiseptic.
-Forget that!
What do we do now?
What about our ship?
The ship we already paid
the down payment for?
Did Mark really leave?
If we fail to pay,
we'll lose the down payment
and may have to pay compensation.
The intermediate payment.
Intermediate payment…
Sell whatever we can
and keep whatever we can,
whether it's a building or a person.
And that includes Typhoon Trading.
TYPHOON TRADING
-What's going on?
-We work here!
-We have the right to know!
Where is your common sense?
Don't just force your way in.
-You have to stop!
-Just go.
Mr. Kang.
-What's going on?
-There's no talking to them. We must go.
-Move aside.
-We cannot do that.
-You need to leave.
-I won't repeat myself.
-Hey!
-Be careful.
See? I told you so.
Move aside.
"Cancelation of Lease"?
DECLARATION OF CLOSURE
CEO: PYO HYUN-JUN
"Declaration of Closure"?
Attorney Choi, go and print another one.
This wasn't what you promised.
Let go of me.
I'm the CEO of this business.
No. You just lost your qualification.
So why did you get cheeky with me?
You should've gotten lost quietly.
You're the one who gave up
and sold off this company, you idiot.
You bastard!
I wasn't thinking straight.
It's my company.
-My company, which you abandoned.
-Stop talking nonsense!
I have never once
given up or abandoned this company.
Just admit it!
You lost, you idiot!
You think I'm the only one you must beat.
I'm nothing, Hyun-jun.
Keep living in that delusion if you want.
You've never fallen behind
and had to stare at someone's back.
What do you know? Damn it.
Typhoon Trading.
Let's go home for today.
You have to come back to work tomorrow.
Oh, dear.
Hang in there a little longer, Dad.
Everything is almost over.
I'll escort you to the hospital soon.
But before we do that,
I need you to do something.
I made an order for a ship.
-A ship?
-Yes, a ship.
The ship you loved so much.
I ordered one
as big as the Panamanian one.
-You crazy idiot.
-What's wrong?
I also kicked out that punk,
Kang Tae-poong,
and took over Typhoon Trading.
On top of that, I bought a merchant ship.
I'm doing everything that you couldn't.
But it turned out to be quite expensive.
So I had to put up something
as collateral to finance it.
Our building.
COLLATERAL OWNER: PYO BAK-HO
Dad.
How do you feel right now?
How does it feel
to be humiliated by your son?
Who…
do you wish…
to win against?
No one.
I've already won against everyone.
I've won already.
I have won!
I'll prove it.
Proceed with this tomorrow.
And I need to move him soon.
Are you sure
about the hospital you looked into?
Yes, it's not on the map, either.
He'll never be found.
Okay, send him away immediately.
I think he's sending him somewhere.
There's been a change!
This way, please.
This way. Come on!
Come on!
Okay! This way!
Are we shipping out from that side today?
The shipment is…
What's the container number?
-One moment.
-Give me that.
Mr. Ha!
The containers on that side are all open.
It looks like someone opened them.
Why were those kept open?
-Everything in Zone 15?
-Yes, sir.
Have you called security?
-Not yet.
-Give me the radio.
You should've radioed them.
That's a part of your work manual!
Security, come to Zone 15.
I didn't know
you could do this, Song-jung.
You're good at this.
I didn't know you were capable of this.
Be careful with that thing in the way.
What? What's that?
What's he doing?
Gosh.
The air's crisp.
PROMISSORY NOTE
You actually found it?
Why didn't you pay my dad back?
You must've had that much money.
I was responsible
for 350 people's livelihood.
That was more frightening.
Keeping them on my payroll
month after month.
Who cares about a promise like this?
In this hellhole,
you're supposed to trample on others
to get yourself out first.
Can you walk by yourself?
You'll let me walk off?
Instead, testify that you received
this promissory note
on the day we promised.
Then I'll return to my business,
and you'll return to yours.
Everything will be the way it was.
What if I turn it down?
I don't care. I'll still let you go.
At least you'll be able
to keep Pyo Merchant Marine.
Those 350 employees you just mentioned.
They also have to make a living.
So you don't care
if Typhoon Trading disappears?
Are you that foolish?
My company isn't something that disappears
just because it has no name.
That's why
we will never go down.
Do you…
expect me to thank you?
What I wanted was an apology.
But I guess
that should be given to my dad.
Hyun-jun must've learned…
from his father
that this world was a hellhole.
My father taught me…
it was full of flowers and fruits.
Well, then.
Good luck to you.
See if the world…
will wait for the flower to bloom…
and the fruit to bear.
-What's this?
-Can't you tell?
I get annoyed when I see the things
you got me, so take them back.
Hey.
-Do you have to go this far?
-What?
I'm much better off than you,
who can't do a thing.
So what if you give me those eyes?
What a joke.
Mi-ho.
-Let go. Let go of me!
-Wait.
All right.
I won't hold you down or stop you,
but just give me a moment.
What are you doing?
Just one moment. It'll take only a second.
Please just come on this day.
Just this one day.
JULY 17TH, 8:00 P.M.
FRONT OF MILLENNIE
Please?
I'll be waiting.
What are you doing?
What's with you?
Gosh.
Things just went haywire, sir.
You know me, sir.
What are you doing?
Come and beg him for forgiveness!
You signed to buy a ship
without my approval…
MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING
SHIP PURCHASE CONTRACT
…got a foreigner involved,
and sold off our company.
Wait, Dad.
It's…
Will you hear me out?
The contract for the ship has been signed,
and the deal is sealed.
You're right, Mr. Pyo Hyun-jun.
You must take responsibility.
-What?
-This is your malfeasance.
You've used
the company's name as you liked.
Mr. Pyo Hyun-jun and Mr. Ha Seong-il.
You two are under arrest without warrant
for malpractice and embezzlement
against Pyo Merchant Marine
as well as suspicions
of arson at the warehouse
in Yeonhwa-dong, Incheon.
Dad.
Let go. Let go of me!
-Dad!
-Mr. Pyo, I have to tell you something.
Let go of me. Let go!
Dad!
Dad! Damn it.
Dad, you saw everything.
I won against that punk.
I won against Tae-poong!
I took him down.
Dad, I won!
Dad.
Dad…
It's all over now.
I'm almost there.
Is that so?
My son.
I lost.
It's my loss.
It wasn't you,
but it was me who lost.
Dad.
Can you just say I did a good job?
I did a good job, right?
What happened to Mr. Kang?
Why haven't we heard from him?
I wonder.
Has he reached out to any of you?
I don't see anyone
from Pyo Merchant Marine or Mr. Kang.
Are you working the night shift today?
I got fired.
I was told to work here starting today.
No news is often the best news.
Let's give him some more time.
Wait, why are you here, Ms. Cha?
The factory's busy right now.
Me? I was told to work here
starting today.
-Says who?
-Who do you think?
Mr. Kang!
-Hey, Mr. Kang!
-Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang!
What's with this red suit?
You look like you're in a boy band.
Three necklaces?
You'll get a neck disk problem.
Your neuralgia must be better.
You can probably button one more.
-Should I do that?
-Yes.
Look.
CEO KANG TAE-POONG
Wonderful.
MILLENNIE STAR SEARCH
Here is the next contestant.
Allow me to introduce you
to our final contestant.
Contestant number…
It's a song he wrote himself.
The title of the song is "Wolf Star."
Please welcome Contestant 13, Wang Nam-mo!
Left behind at the end of the night
You flowed by in your loneliness
Without a word
You crossed winter with a blank face
Casting a shadow
And fading away
I wish to reach you beyond this dark night
When the world shakes like it'll crash
I'll stay right here
In the season where you stood still
In that sky
I'll stay here and shine upon you
Even when everything disappears
Even when I can no longer shine
With all my strength
I will remain in your sky
This cold and painful season
Passing through
Wasn't I cool?
No.
Mi-ho.
I will
try my best without giving up.
But that means I may not end up rich.
Took you long enough, stupid.
Instead,
I'll sing for you every single day,
make you laugh, and wipe your tears.
I'll stay by your side forever.
-Be happy!
-Congrats!
TYPHOON TRADING
Isn't that cool?
You can save music in here.
How many songs?
-Up to 32 songs.
-What? Let me see that.
Do you know what's crazier?
You can erase it and save new songs.
How many times? No way!
Infinitely.
No way.
What is the pricing range
for this particular product?
It's expensive. It's not cheap.
However,
think of what this thing can do.
It's 250,000 won, but it's not much.
It's 250,000 won?
How do you put songs in here?
You have to download files
by accessing the Internet.
There are websites.
So you can't use this without a computer?
I don't think it's a bad idea.
It's tiny, and I can only listen
to the music I like.
I'll eat my hat
if even a single person buys that.
I got a cosmetics product.
A cosmetics product? So cliché.
This company
had been researching diabetes,
then came across
this new substance great for skin.
They continued their research,
and ended up developing it
into a cosmetic product.
But France is still more well-known
for cosmetics products, isn't it?
I thought what we needed
was a change in the way we think,
like this company that made this
while researching for medicine.
Foreign brands aren't necessarily better.
Korea could be the best, you know.
It just needs to be good quality.
In that case,
may I take it home and try it out?
-Of course.
-Okay.
Gosh.
Goodness.
ROSE DELIVERY
FROM HONEY-POONG
Wait a second.
What are you two up to? What was that?
Mr. Kang, look me in the eyes.
Why did you squint your eyes?
There was something in my eyes.
There wasn't anything.
Don't you know that they're dating?
Goodness.
Everyone in this world knows
except for you three here.
It was so obvious.
Yes, they're the OC. The office couple.
Wait, so they held hands and stuff?
Cut it out.
You shouldn't do that at work.
We'll be having galbitang soon.
Well, well.
Are you going to stay?
Are you okay with this?
What if he ends up fainting?
Beom.
Are you that heartbroken?
Come here. Come to me.
There, there.
What's so heartbreaking
about Mi-ho getting married?
She'll come by often.
I knew that guy would do this.
I should've kicked him out while I could.
My goodness.
Hey, Beom.
I'm here for you.
And Tae-poong, right?
Don't even mention that punk.
There's no use in bringing up a son.
Mi-seon has been
coming home late, hasn't she?
I know.
Well, both you and I are
in the same situation.
Mi-ja now has a boyfriend too.
You're right.
All right.
So?
You two are getting married?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Good.
Yes, ma'am.
We went ahead and found a good date
for our family meeting and the wedding.
Oh, dear.
Congratulations, young lady.
Ma'am,
our family isn't too well-off,
so we couldn't prepare much.
Please take a look.
-I got you a new outfit.
-Goodness.
And a set of silverware.
Oh, my. These look wonderful.
And before winter comes,
we'll get you a new set of bedding.
Why, thank you.
In my case,
I wanted to offer you this.
It once belonged to my daughter-in-law.
-Oh, my.
-It's for you.
What are you doing? Take it.
No, it's not for her. It's yours.
You've done well in raising your son.
Ma'am…
I named that girl.
I named her Mi-ho
because I wanted her to laugh a lot.
So make sure she laughs a lot.
Come on!
You're the worst, Grandma.
But she cries too often.
Make sure she laughs more.
So, Mr. Wang, have you sold lots of silk?
Silk?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
You can't eat this alone.
-Do you want one?
-Yes.
Should I eat the whole thing?
Have a seat.
-I have--
-I have something for you.
Come on.
-What is it?
-You first, then.
Well…
-Is this it?
-Yes.
Why don't we exchange these
on the count of three?
Okay, where's yours?
Where do you think it is?
-One, two.
-Three.
Here. What's this?
-That's for you.
-It's heavy.
-May I open it?
-Of course.
What are these?
Flower seeds.
What are these? Workbooks?
"Class pass"?
-For the college entrance exam?
-Yes.
You've always wanted to go to college.
But you couldn't take the test back then.
I want you to continue with your studies
just like you wanted.
Gosh, flower seeds?
That was your dream, Tae-poong.
But a plant nursery
was too expensive for me to get.
I'll make much more money
and buy you a plant nursery.
No.
I no longer need
a plant nursery.
You told me that…
stars still exist
even when they can't be seen.
I thought about it
and realized all my flowers were here.
I found my sentiment too.
This place is full of my dreams.
Here at Typhoon Trading.
YEONGIL ACADEMY CLASS PASS
You know what?
I've always wanted to become a trader.
I know I can do my job very well
without a university diploma.
And I have
both Typhoon Trading and you, Tae-poong.
I think I'm pretty okay
just the way I am right now.
No way.
Ms. Oh Mi-seon,
you're awesome.
Out of all the people I've met,
you're the prettiest.
What do you think, Mom?
It's a bit too small, isn't it?
It's so nice.
Really? Let's have a look at the door.
Does this open well?
Goodness, you have a wonderful son.
And it's tough to find
an apartment at this price.
Here.
So?
Do you want to look at a few more?
Tae-poong.
Why don't we stay
at that place a little longer?
Is it inconvenient for you?
I'd love to do that,
but our room gets cold in winter.
I'm worried that you'll fall and get hurt.
Oh, my.
Mi-seon may be stingy,
but she doesn't hold back on briquettes.
Let's find a bigger place later
and all move in together.
I mean, there's Ms. Bun-i and Beom.
We can't just leave them alone.
I'd feel too guilty to fall asleep.
Gosh.
I must've taken after you, Mom.
Of course. You're just like me.
You're good at everything.
And you're so cool.
I mean, how are we so softhearted
even when we're completely broke?
Who cares about money?
We have everything else.
Dad treasured and protected us so dearly.
He did.
I've received so much.
I thought I had nothing left.
We were left with lots.
We're so rich.
Okay, then. Let me think.
Ms. Bun-i, Beom, Mi-seon, you, and me,
the five of us have to live together.
I'll have to share a room with Ms. Bun-i,
and Beom is growing up
and needs his own space.
So he needs a room.
Then you and Ms. Oh, so four rooms?
Will it be too expensive?
-We need three rooms, don't we?
-Why three?
Mi-seon and I will share one.
You're thinking of that already?
There's no use in raising a son.
-I was just joking.
-You're lying.
WELCOME TYPHOON TRADING
ON "EXPERIENCE LIFE ON SITE"
That looks hot. We might die today.
So will it really help Typhoon Trading
to go on this show?
Yes, of course.
These days, we have to market ourselves
and get noticed.
Hey, don't even ask. Look at his eyes.
He's not in the right state.
Anyway, this cauldron looks heavy.
Will it cost a lot to transport?
Mr. Bae, when we get back, can you look up
the freight cost to South America?
Meat cooks well in these cauldrons.
-Yes.
-In my opinion,
you're the weirdest one here, Ms. Oh.
Hey, the cameras are here. Smile.
-Smile.
-Hello.
-How's it working out?
-We haven't started yet.
This will be tough.
EXPERIENCE LIFE ON SITE
You're watching MBS here in Seoul, Korea.
"Experience Life on Site."
A trading company leading Korea
out into the global world,
please welcome CEO Kang Tae-poong
and Typhoon Trading!
Come on out!
-All right! Come on in.
-Hello.
-There are many of them.
-They have such great teamwork.
-They all came here together.
-Yes, and the CEO is quite good-looking.
-Yes, he's such a handsome boy.
-Yes.
I'd like to give him ten out of ten.
-Ms. Cha, your makeup makes you look ill.
-It's great to have you here.
-I heard they had a rough day.
-Look at Mr. Koo. He thinks he's an actor.
It would've looked much better
if you sat in the first row.
Look ahead. We're on air. Please.
-You want to show off your girlfriend?
-All right.
A small business in Korea
creating quite the buzz,
Typhoon Trading will take us
to a paradise of cauldrons!
Let's take a look!
All right.
All you have to do
is melt the scrap iron here
to make a cauldron.
How long will it take?
You'll have to finish everything today,
and it takes about 11 hours.
It looks tough, doesn't it?
I told you.
Let's go!
Looking great!
-Going in.
-Keep pouring!
-Let's go!
-One, two, three.
-Careful.
-Okay.
-Lift this?
-Yes.
Gosh.
Gosh, that's hot.
My gosh.
Even the food is charred.
It's because soot fell from your face.
I need ketchup when I'm eating sausages.
It's heavy.
-It's so heavy.
-Goodness.
The food isn't much, is it?
-No, it's good.
-It's good.
I'm so sorry.
Koreans draw strength from rice!
Even the IMF crisis couldn't stand
against the power of a good meal.
It's good.
Their bodies may be covered in soot,
but the small envelope in their hands
stand as proof of their sweat and time,
a testament to how they endured
and overcame their darkest days.
All right! Great work, everyone.
One crucial step remains.
Of course. So how much did you make?
The six of us made 50,000 each,
so 300,000 won.
-Great work!
-Great work.
Now, everyone.
A small Korean business, Typhoon Trading,
did something quite meaningful.
Now, please donate the money
for a great cause to help those in need!
Wait! No!
-Ms. Oh, come here!
-Hey!
It's now. Get on it with me.
I don't want to. I'm scared of heights.
-No, you can go.
-Come with me.
No, you can do it. I don't want to.
Move aside.
I always wanted to be a prince.
Lift it up, please.
That's so irrelevant.
Hey, don't you know
the ladies are always first?
Be careful.
-The unicorn might end up breaking.
-Right.
I didn't want to say this,
but I'm the CEO.
Yes, you must feel sad,
but let the CEO have his moment.
-At least let me hold the tail.
-Come on down.
-Okay.
-Honey.
Are you watching this?
Happy wedding anniversary to us.
-You've put up with me long enough now…
-Wait.
Give it up for Typhoon Trading!
Go on up!
Are you ready to go up?
Here we go!
-Whoa.
-Watch it.
Mom!
TOTAL AMOUNT: 8,027,010 WON
THE FUNDS WILL BE USED FOR A GOOD CAUSE
COUNTING DOWN TO THE 2002 WORLD CUP
FACELESS SINGERS ARE ON THE RISE!
WAX AND BROWN EYES
COUNTING DOWN TO THE 2002 WORLD CUP
KANG TAE-POONG
CEO OF TYPHOON TRADING
Just as the sun always rises
after the dark passes by,
if you hang on through your tough day,
you will come out stronger tomorrow.
CEO KANG TAE-POONG
There is a small business
somewhere in Ulchiro
that stayed strong
through the dark times of the IMF crisis
and continued
to stay in business to this day.
CHA SEON-TAEK
GENERAL MANAGER
People say computers are accurate,
but I still believe the human hand
is faster and more accurate.
What? A battle with the computer?
It's impossible for humans
to lose against a computer.
GO MA-JIN
DEPUTY GENERAL MANAGER
Times may change,
but I believe there are timeless things.
Well, it's nothing much.
But family love, comradeship,
and patriotism.
AUGUST EVENTS AND PLANS
Things like those.
TOTAL QUANTITY: 950 UNIT/BOXES
TOTAL WEIGHT: 6,300 KGS
BAE SONG-JUNG
MANAGER
Send me a friend request.
Mr. Kang and I
raised these orchids together.
KOO MYEONG-GWAN
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR
People say, "Without haste, without rest."
-If you continue to work hard, you will--
-Cut!
Gosh, isn't this way too dull?
Me?
-What's so bad about the flowers?
-Over there.
Excuse me.
Can we get an interview with you?
Me?
I believe we need the courage
to take another step amid a crisis.
How can I put this?
OH MI-SEON
MANAGER
It may be tough to do alone,
but together, it's probably possible.
Oh, our company?
There will be difficulties for sure.
But CEO Kang Tae-poong
and all of us share the idea
that if we do not give up,
anything is possible.
After all, it's all done by people.
That means
we're the ones that make it happen.
Just like this, Korea did not fall apart
despite a huge danger like the IMF crisis,
thanks to these small businesses
that have taken deep roots in our society.
Reporting from Typhoon Trading--
Ms. Oh, we're late for the game company.
-Let's go.
Excuse us.
-What?
-Pardon me.
-Bye.
-I'm Seo Seok-gyu from Typhoon Trading.
KEONNAM UNIVERSITY SUMMER
SOCCER TOURNAMENT CHAMPIONS
RECRUITING MEMBERS FOR THE DRAMA CLUB
Hey, hop in.
-What?
-He's cute.
He was talking to you!
-Let's go.
-Okay.
"Hop in"?
It's been a while, so I wanted to do it.
You're with Next Revolution,
the gaming company, right?
Yes, but…
Are you really buying all these?
IMMORTAL GORYEO
BUBBLE BUBBLE BANG ADVENTURE
Why are you helping me?
We're helping him?
No, we believe in the value of these items
and in your future.
However, promise us one thing
that you won't give up
and take this to the end.
Hey, guys. Hop in!
Number 17, Oh Beom.
Congeniality Award.
Oh, my. Congeniality Award.
My boy got the Congeniality Award.
Oh, my.
Should I let him go to an art college?
His work is titled, "My Family."
DRAWING CONTEST
MY FAMILY
The dot-com bubble
is a huge problem right now.
So why don't we try exporting games?
Isn't that something Japan is good at?
You're right,
but they're strong with console games.
You know, the game cartridges
you stick into a machine.
Yes, I know what that is. Game Man.
-Yes.
-I got my kid a few.
But computer games are different.
First, it doesn't require a console.
Also, the graphics are wonderful.
A strategy game based on the Goryeo era.
I've never seen anything like this.
It's like the Asian medieval times.
So why don't we invest a little
to localize the game a bit more?
We can make different characters
for different countries,
and find the best translators too.
We're not simply selling games.
We're selling culture.
That sounds like lunch.
What time is it? Goodness.
Shouldn't we line up?
-Oh, my. Let's go.
-Let's go.
Anyway, why has Mr. Bae
been making that face?
I'm trying to be the Smiling Angel.
Eat well.
-Stop it.
-Cut it out.
Should I be the Smiling Devil, then?
Dad.
I loved flowers.
They were pretty and fragrant.
I thought my world
would always be filled with things
that were beautiful and good.
Then let's do this.
We'll all eat lunch together,
and then play this game.
I was devastated
when that world came crashing down.
I thought
my life would face
an insignificant ending.
Today, Korea has officially
broken free from the IMF system.
At the time of the financial crisis
in late 1997,
Korea borrowed $19.5 billion
from the IMF but paid it back
in just three years and eight months,
three years before the deadline.
Korea has restored sovereignty
over our economy once again.
Reporter Park Jang-beom.
But still, when I turned my face,
I realized my flowers were here.
My sunshine.
My rain.
My wind.
They had all been here.
I now know where my flowers are.
I'm no longer lost.
At times, we'll face cold seasons.
The pitch-black darkness
will find us again.
But still,
I won't give up…
for my flowers.
No,
for my people.
FINAL EPISODE
WE MET THE BLUEBIRD, AND LIFE GOES ON
TYPHOON FAMILY
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn